https://www.valdezmuseum.org/privacy-policy/

Valdez Museum & Historical Archive
Make a Donation Join & SupportMembershipWays of GivingOur SponsorsVolunteerAbout usBoard of DirectorsStaffCareer OpportunitiesPress ReleasesCalendarContact usHost an event
New Museum ProjectGet InvolvedInvest In The New MuseumGift AnnouncementsProject UpdatesImage GalleryVisitExhibitsPermanentValdez Museum on EganValdez Museum on HazeletTemporary ExhibitsCurrent ExhibitPast ExhibitsUpcoming ExhibitsOnline ExhibitsResourcesCommunities, Disaster, and Change BlogAudioFact SheetsAlyeska Pipeline Marine Terminal ConstructionAviationCopper Valley CommunitiesHealth CareValdez CentennialHistory of ValdezEducationAt the MuseumIn the ClassroomOutreachResourcesCollectionsArchiveOnline CollectionsGold Rush Names DatabaseShopBooks & MediaChildren’sAlaskan ArtAlaskan Plants & WildlifeAlaskan Native History & CultureKlondike Gold RushStatehoodSkiing Alaska and Snow SafetyAlaskan Bush PilotsIditarodWorking in AlaskaTrue Alaskan AdventuresAlaskan FictionAlaskan Young AdultAlaskan CookbooksDVDs & MusicClearanceToys & GamesGiftsOne of a KindArtJewelryMuseumTicketsMembershipsCurrent Exhibit Menu
Privacy Policy You are here: Home
Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyThe Valdez Museum & Historical Archive  is concerned about the protection of the privacy of its Web site visitors, members and donors. We respect your privacy and your choice not to have your personal information shared with other people. Your use of our Web site indicates your acceptance of this Privacy Policy.Web Site InformationThe Museum only collects personal contact information (such as names, addresses, e-mail addresses and phone numbers) when users submit it voluntarily. To make our Web site more useful to you, our server automatically collects information when you visit our site, such as, but not limited to, your IP address, date and time of your visit, pages viewed and click streams. We will not collect or track information that may identify you personally. We do not share this data to any 3rd parties or use it for any commercial purposes other than the ones outlined in this document.  You can request removing your data by contacting us at 907-835-2764 or info@valdezmuseum.org Mailing AddressWe will not use, sell or exchange your mailing or e-mail addresses. We use only those addresses which are submitted voluntarily when asked for consent to be contacted further by the Museum.Terms of UseBy using this Web site and its content, you agree to be bound by and acknowledge your acceptance of the following Terms of Use and applicable laws. By accessing and browsing this Web site you fully acknowledge and accept the following terms and conditions.CopyrightImages, text, software, documentation, electronic text and image files, audio and video clips and other materials are the property of the Museum and will be protected by restrictions for use. Furthermore, copyrights and other proprietary rights in the materials on this site may belong to individuals and entities other than the Museum.The Museum expressly prohibits the copying of any protected materials on this Web site, except for the purposes of fair use as defined by copyright law and as described below. This prohibition includes the downloading of site content for commercial use or for use on personal Web sites.Fair UseFair use of copyrighted material includes the use of protected materials for noncommercial educational purposes, such as teaching, scholarship, research, criticism, commentary and news reporting. Users who wish to download or print text and image files from the Museum’s Web site for such uses must request the Museum’s express permission by contacting info@valdezmuseum.org. Users must cite the author and source for this material as they would material from any printed work and the citation should include the URL <https://www.valdezmuseum.org.> None of the content may be altered or modified.DisclaimerThe text, images and content on this Web site are provided “as is” without a warranty of any kind, either expressed or implied, including but not limited to the implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular use and/or non-infringement. The removal of any digital watermark, propriety notices or accompanying text that may be included on or with the image is prohibited. The Museum assumes no responsibility, and shall not be liable, for any damage or viruses that may infect your computer equipment or other property on account of your use of the site or your downloading of any text, images or content from the Web site. You acknowledge that if you rely on any information or content on the Web site, you do so solely at your own risk.ContactAnyone wishing to use any of the files or images contained on this Web site for publication or any purpose other than fair use as defined by law must request and receive prior permission from the Museum. The responsibility for determining whether any third-party rights exist and for obtaining all other necessary permissions remains solely with the user and the Museum will have no responsibility in connection with securing such rights for any materials on the Web site. Any other use, such as, without limitation, the use of an image for a commercial purpose, requires the prior written consent of the Museum, which may be granted or denied at the Museum’s sole discretion. The failure by the Museum to insist upon or enforce strict performance of any provision of the Terms of Use by you or others will not be construed as a waiver of any provision or right of the Museum or other entities’ rights. All requests to reproduce artwork in any form from the Museum’s collection must be submitted in writing to:Valdez Museum & Historical Archive PO Box 8 Valdez, AK 99686 907.835.2764 info@valdezmuseum.org
Calendar<<Dec 2020>>SMTWTFS 29 30 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 23 24 25 26 27 28 29 30 31 1 2   Back to topNew Museum ProjectGet InvolvedInvest In The New MuseumProject UpdatesImage GalleryVisitExhibitsPermanentTemporary ExhibitsOnline ExhibitsResourcesEducationAt the MuseumIn the ClassroomOutreachResourcesCollectionsArchiveOnline CollectionsGold Rush Names DatabaseShopBooks & MediaToys & GamesGiftsOne of a KindMuseum MuseumJoin & SupportAbout usCalendarContact usHost an eventCurrent hoursEgan Location:Your safety is our priority!Main Museum is open with new health guidelines that ensure a safe environment for visitors and staff. Hours: Tuesday - Sunday, 12 - 4 pm.Closed Monday Hazelet Location:Remains closed for the season, but will be available to researchers by appointment only.  Locations217 Egan Dr.
Valdez, AK 99686
(907) 835-2764436 S. Hazelet
Valdez, AK 99686
(907) 835-5407P.O. Box 8 Valdez, AK 99686 E-News
© 2020 Valdez Museum & Historical Archive.
Design by Sound Web SolutionsSitemapPrivacy PolicyBoard LoginAdmin LoginCollectionsBlue Star Museums
